“You should love God with your whole heart, your soul, etc.”
«Dovresti amare Dio con tutto il cuore, con tutta l'anima, ecc. ».
All right, good. And that God, what does he look like?
Giusto, bene. E quel Dio, che aspetto ha?
[God’s Facebook Profile]
[Il Profilo Facebook Di Dio]
Is he alone?
E' da solo?
What does he do?
Che fa?
Where does he live?
Dove vive?
That seems to be a natural question.
Sembra essere una domanda normale.
This God that we should love with our whole heart
Questo Dio che dovremmo amare con tutto il cuore
and soul and everything, do you have a picture of him?
e l'anima e ogni cosa, ne hai un'immagine?
Show me what he looks like.
Mostrami che aspetto ha.
If I said, “There’s this girl, or guy,
Se dicessi: «C'è una ragazza, o un ragazzo,
and you’re gonna love them with your whole heart and soul”,
e li amerai con tutto il tuo cuore e la tua anima»,
and the first thing … you go, “Can I see ’em?”
e la prima cosa... chiederesti: «Posso vederli?»
“Well, no, that would be offensive.”
«Beh, no, sarebbe offensivo».
[Laughing]
[ride]
I mean, it’s common sense. Why is it called “FACEbook”?
Ossia, è buon senso. Perché si chiama "FACEbook"?
Why?
Perché?
Does it have anything to do with faces?
Ha qualcosa a che vedere con le facce?
Maybe? Looking at faces?
Forse? Guardare delle facce?
And saying, “I like this face, and this one I don’t like as much”?
E dire: «Mi piace questa faccia, e quest'altra non mi piace tanto».
So people, they want a social network with God, but no pictures.
Allora le persone, vogliono una relazione "social" con Dio, ma senza immagini.
Why?
Perché?
Why are they afraid?
Perché hanno paura?
Is God married? Does He have a girlfriend?
Dio è sposato? Ha una fidanzata?
Is He in a relationship?
Ha una relazione?
[Laughing]
[ride]
Relationship status: Complicated.
Relazione: complicata.